Search

Legal Info / Policy Info
========================

What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. Google uses of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

* To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).
* To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

Do we use cookies?

Yes, Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other ueses.

When you use our website, we share information that we collect from you, such as your email (in hashed form), IP address or information about your browser or operating system, with our partner/service provider, LiveRamp Inc. LiveRamp returns an online identification code that we may store in our first-party cookie for our use in online and cross-channel advertising and it may be shared with advertising companies to enable interest-based and targeted advertising. To opt out of this use, please [click here](https://liveramp.com/opt_out)

For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for interest-based advertising purposes, please visit [Your Ad Choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by clicking here

General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) Compliance

For persons located in the European Economic Area (“EU Data Subjects”), commencing on May 25th, 2018 and in case of inquiries to our affiliated companies in Europe (such as orders or applications), we will process your personal information in accordance with the Regulations (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) according to which you have the following rights: 1.You have the right to information as to whether or not and to which extent we process which of your personal information. 2.You have the right to object the processing of your data based on Article 6 (1) (e), (f) of the GDPR on grounds relating to your particular situation at any time. 3.You have the right to rectification of any inaccurate personal information about you and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to have any incomplete personal data about you completed. 4.You have the right to the erasure of your personal information without undue delay unless we have a legitimate interest to keep the information, such as in the event we need the information to execute an agreement with you. 5.You have the right to restrict the processing of your personal information, unless we have a legitimate interest to continue processing the information for the purpose in respect to which you requested the restriction. For example, you have the right to object to our processing of your personal information for direct marketing purposes (including profiling for direct marketing purposes). If you make such an objection, we will cease to process your personal information for this purpose. You have the right to receive your personal information from us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format – data portability. However, this right does not apply where it would adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others. 6.You have the right to withdraw your previously given consent at any time. If you are an EU Data Subject and wish to exercise any of the foregoing rights, you should contact us at legal@blitz.gg. If you believe our processing of your personal information violates data protection laws, you have a legal right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority responsible for data protection. You may do so in the EU member state of your habitual residence, your place of work or the place of the alleged violation. You may exercise any of your rights in this section in relation to your personal data by written notice to us at the following email address: legal@blitz.gg. For EU Data Subjects, we rely on the following legal bases to process your personal information: 1.The legal bases for the processing of information we obtain while you visit our Sites or use our Services are the performance of a contract with respect to the use of our Sites and Services (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b GDPR) and our legitimate interests (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f GDPR) in improving the performance of our Sites and Services. 2.The legal basis for the processing of information we obtain through email messages or forms is your consent (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a GDPR). 3.The legal basis for the processing of obtained information related to your interest in purchasing our products and Services is Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b GDPR (steps at the request of the data subject prior to entering into a contract). 4.The legal bases for the processing of information we obtain in the course of your registration are performance of a contract (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b GDPR) and your consent (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a GDPR). 5.The legal basis for the processing of information we obtain through your subscription to our e-mail alerts and/or newsletters is your consent (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. a GDPR). 6.The legal basis for the processing of information we obtain through the use of cookies, web beacons and third party analytics is our legitimate interests (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f GDPR) in improving the performance of our Sites and analyzing its use. 7.The legal basis for the transmission of information to third-party contractors, agents, business partners, sales representatives, or service providers is performance of the contract (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. b GDPR) and legitimate interest (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f GDPR). 8.The legal basis for the transmission of information to third parties in case we become involved in a merger, acquisition, sale of assets, securities offering, bankruptcy, reorganization, dissolution, or any other transaction is our legitimate interest (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f GDPR) in preparing and executing the applicable measure. 9.The legal basis for the transmission of information to law enforcement, governmental agencies, or authorized third parties is the compliance with a legal obligation (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. c GDPR). 10.The legal basis for the transmission of information to our legal counsel and other consultants in connection with actual or potential litigation is our legitimate interest (Art. 6 Para. 1 lit. f GDPR) in receiving consulting services. We will only send EU Data Subjects marketing emails or contact EU Data Subjects regarding marketing matters where they have agreed to this, such as by subscribing to our newsletters, email lists, filling out our contact forms or sending us email inquiries. As noted above, we may personalize the message content based upon any information you have provided to us and your use of the Sites. If you subscribe to a newsletter you will be needed to confirm your e-mail address by clicking on a link in an e-mail conformation we send you (double-opt-in). Set & edit your privacy choices here

Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.

Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website [here](https://blitz.gg/terms-of-service).

Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. This policy was last modified on October 26, 2023.

Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information here. This policy is powered by Trust Guard PCI compliant security scanning.
